blindsgalore.com 1999-11-18

# Privacy Policy

| 

### Privacy and You 

At Blindsgalore.com (a division of QVDS, Inc.) your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That is why, when you visit our Internet site [www.blindsgalore.com](http://www.blindsgalore.com/) we help you maintain control over your personal information on the Internet. We use the information we collect about you only to process orders and to provide other enhanced shopping features. Please read on for more detail about our privacy policy. ** **

**Blindsgalore.com only asks for specific types of personal information** : **** we request information from you when you:

1.       Place an order on blindsgalore.com

2.       Provide feedback

3.       Participate in a contest, sweepstake, or other promotional offer

4.       Request notification of your order status via e-mail, telephone, fax, or mail

5.       Subscribe to a mailing list or a newsletter.

When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your orders and to notify you of your order status. When you voluntarily sign up for our e-mail notification service, we need only an e-mail address that we use to send the information you requested.  When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. In the case of mailing lists and newsletters, you will be able to unsubscribe to these mailings at any time.

#### Blindsgalore.com uses your personal information for specific purposes: The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with QVDS, Inc., d.b.a. Blindsgalore.com. We want you to be able to quickly find information on blindsgalore.com and alert you to product updates, special offers, upgrades, and other new products and services. Agents and associates of blindsgalore.com who have access to your information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for QVDS, Inc. 

**You can opt-out of receiving further marketing from blindsgalore.com at any time** : **** We will send you information about various products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only QVDS, Inc. (or agents working on behalf of QVDS, Inc. and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive any such information and mailings, you can easily opt-out of our mailing list by sending e-mail to [remove@blindsgalore.com](mailto:remove@blindsgalore.com)

**Blindsgalore.com will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent** : Information about you, such as your name, address, telephone number, your order, and the products you purchase, is kept confidential. This information may be shared with agents and associates of blindsgalore.com only for the purpose of performing services for QVDS, Inc. d.b.a. Blindsgalore.com. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.

**Blindsgalore.com wants to help you keep your personal information accurate** : **** You can request the information that we have collected about you via the Internet at [webmaster@blindsgalore.com](mailto:webmaster@blindsgalore.com). You can also have factual inaccuracies in this information corrected by contacting [webmaster@blindsgalore.com](mailto:webmaster@blindsgalore.com).

**Internet Commerce** : **** The blindsgalore.com web site is designed to give you options regarding the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail, phone number, and any other information that you provide us. When you place orders or access your account, all of our information is processed through a secure server. Blindsgalore.com utilizes industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that encrypts all information you input, before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may place an order without the credit card information, and a customer service representative will contact you. Alternatively, you may always contact a sales representative over the telephone by simply calling **1-877-70-BLIND**. It has always been our practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase. 

#### What about "cookies"?  “Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. At Blindsgalore.com, we primarily use “cookies” in our shopping cart area. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to deliver a customized visitor experience when you visit [www.blindsgalore.com](http://www.blindsgalore.com/). QVDS, Inc., d.b.a. Blindsgalore.com has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the blindsgalore.com web site. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them. 

**About third party Internet sites** : Third party Internet sites and services accessible through blindsgalore.com have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. QVDS, Inc., d.b.a. Blindsgalore.com has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies and actions. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. While we strive to protect your personal information, QVDS, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us   

#### Your Consent: By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by QVDS, Inc., d.b.a. Blindsgalore.com.  Any changes in our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose this information. 

#### Tell us what you think: Blindsgalore.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send e-mail to [feedback@blindsgalore.com](mailto:feedback@blindsgalore.com).
